{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "可乐",
      "answer": "Kělè | coke"
    },
    {
      "question": "雪碧",
      "answer": "Xuěbì | sprite"
    },
    {
      "question": "啤酒",
      "answer": "Píjiǔ | beer"
    },
    {
      "question": "牛奶",
      "answer": "Niúnǎi | milk"
    },
    {
      "question": "汉堡",
      "answer": "Hànbǎo | hamburger"
    },
    {
      "question": "热狗",
      "answer": "Règǒu | hotdog"
    },
    {
      "question": "面包",
      "answer": "Miànbāo | bread"
    },
    {
      "question": "中餐",
      "answer": "Zhōngcān | chinese food"
    },
    {
      "question": "西餐",
      "answer": "Xīcān | western food"
    },
    {
      "question": "茶",
      "answer": "Chá | tea"
    },
    {
      "question": "米饭",
      "answer": "Mǐfàn | (cooked) rice"
    },
    {
      "question": "女儿",
      "answer": "Nǚ'ér | daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "儿子",
      "answer": "Érzi | son"
    },
    {
      "question": "晚上",
      "answer": "Wǎnshàng | evening"
    },
    {
      "question": "店",
      "answer": "Diàn | store or shop"
    }
  ]
}
